The license plate matches
a stolen vehicle report.
The car is stolen.
I repeat. the car is stolen.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Stop!
Step out of the car
with your hands in the air!
So what do we do now?
This is your last warning!
Step out of the car!
We let both cars
reach the middle of the bridge.
What?
You're crazy!
- They'll back down.
- Why would they back down?
- Stop the vehicle immediately!
- Because I'm not gonna.
Stop the car. right now!
Now they have to turn around.
And those extra seconds will be precious.
Unbelievable!
And I thought I was the crazy one.
Clearly. you're the nutcase.
How about we take a walk
in the woods under the pale moonlight?
I'd love to.
Don't you find
that we make a romantic couple?
Young lovers on a yacht.
preparing a new heist…
The perfect couple.
And we even have a full moon.
Hey. babe. look.
The Golden Tower is all lit up for us.
Our first kiss was on a boat.
Maybe it's a sign
we should get one and live on it.
You know. somewhere like…
Venice or. um… Amsterdam.
Doesn't it rain too much?
All the better for us.
We'll stay in bed all day.
C'mon. answer it.
It's your mother. She might be sick again.
It's okay. Mom.
Don't worry. You're not bothering me.
Are you okay?
For the past 17 days.
I've been listening to those silly chimes.
Imagine how I feel.
All day I keep looking at my phone.
hoping for a message from you.
And when it arrives. I'm afraid to look.
I'm afraid that it might be
your last message to me.
But then I think about how beautiful it
would be if you felt the same way too.
So. I open it.
"Never in my life have I felt
the way I did
when I walked up those steps
to the attic with you."
When I read your message.
I ran out of my house
and didn't stop running until it was dark.
It was like a dream.
I felt the same.
All I wanted to do was to wait
by the door and watch you run back to me.
hot and your shirt covered in sweat.
and me wrapped in it.
And… as I look at the Golden Tower.
I'm blind to its beauty
because all I can think of is you.
I gotta go now.
I guess you're thinking.
"Wow. what a weird conversation
to have with your mother." Huh?
No. you can have
whatever conversation you want.
You don't want to ask me.
but I'm still gonna tell you.
It's just that Bruce
decided to say goodbye
to his past life and throw a party.
He was saying goodbye
to partying and traveling
and… sleeping around
with thousands of girls.
He was saying goodbye
to the life he had before meeting me.
And do you know
why he wanted to end all of that?
Because he's in love with me.
And now all he wants to do
is snuggle up on the sofa.
watching movies
and eating popcorn together every night.
But… I've never experienced
all these things he's grown tired of.
Is that necessarily a bad thing?
If you're happy.
I was a virgin. Roi.
A 36-year-old virgin who had only
gotten laid through her VR headset.
- Okay…
- Bruce is the only man I've had sex with.
Not anymore.
Someone new has come into my life.
This guy has swept me off my feet.
It's like an obsession.
I'm sorry. I was cleaning myself up.
and I fell asleep.
I should go.
No. stay. I'll go. It's okay.
Bye.
Thank you.
I wanted to open the door.
Or maybe I didn't.
Ha! Do it!
Hey! Are you done in there?
Some of us have to pee!
How are we gonna get out?
It was an irrational attraction.
My brain had stopped working.
And suddenly. I didn't care anymore.
I could hear all the noise.
the music. the voices.
but above it all.
I could hear his heart beating.
Pum-pum… Pum-pum…
Pounding like at a rock concert.
And I can't explain it. but…
I didn't feel guilty or scared.
I just wanted to be there.
Naked against his skin…
as he carried me through the crowd.
And I would have gone anywhere with him.
Crashing in the ocean from way above
Got the music in you. baby
Tell me why
You've been locked in here forever
And you just can't say goodbye…
I remember beams of light
streaming into the attic.
Like a lighthouse.
And the sound of glass chimes
moving in the air.
I was drowning in waves of orgasms.
though he begged me
to wait until we came at the same time.
and I grabbed the carpet with my nails--
Thank you. Enough.
I get the picture. I know what you mean.
Listen. Keila.
usually. I would say
it's better to forget about it.
It's just a fling.
But considering
what I heard you say to your "mother."
maybe this is something serious.
I didn't think this would lead
to anything either.
but then he said something
that changed everything.
I'd really like to see you again.
Are you good with numbers?
I'd say it's my specialty.
655-347-949.
And now his number
is tattooed inside my brain.
and I'll never forget it. even if I'm old
and frail. dying with Alzheimer's.
The first three days.
I managed not to text him.
But on the fourth day…
In the beginning. it was
just a few messages each day. but now…
Now we text each other like 30 times a day
and maybe more.
And once he called me in front of Bruce.
I saved his number on my phone
as "Mom." so he's not suspicious.
I told him that she wasn't well.
I pretended that
she had some kinda kidney problem.
It's driving me crazy. Roi.
I'm in love with Bruce.
but at the same time.
I'm hoping Claudio will call me.
And if he doesn't text me.
I repeat in my head over and over again
the previous messages
that I've learned by heart.
- Are you sure you love Bruce?
- Yes. of course. I do.
That's why I haven't seen Claudio
since the party and why we only text.
What?
- It's much worse.
- What do you mean?
Hoping that he'll text you is worse
than screwing in the bathroom.
Keila. one-night stands
can happen to us all.
And we get over it. and we move on.
But spending all day
waiting for the phone to ring.
hoping it's him.
reading his messages.
remembering moments you've shared…
Keila.
You know you're cheating on Bruce.
You changed the guy's name to "Mom"
on your phone. That says it all.
He deserves better.
Rise and shine!
Sun's up! Get out of bed! A new day calls!
Wakey. wakey. people!
No rest for the wicked!
A new day has dawned!
I know what you're all thinking. Mm?
You're wondering.
why's he serving breakfast?
Why's he still wearing yesterday's
dirty clothes?
And two bullet holes in his chest.
What's with that?
To be precise. they're not real bullets.
They're toy pellets.
Well. let's just say
that I am currently experiencing things…
that I have never experienced
in my life before.
What things?
My wallet was stolen.
A master stroke.
an act of pure… prestidigitation.
And then I experienced
a magical night together with this woman…
This is the same woman who shot me.
And it's not important!
The woman fascinates me.
And that's what's so surprising.
Because. Candela…
Her name's Candela.
…represents just about everything
I've disapproved of my entire adult life.
And what are
these things you disapprove of?
I've never had time
for these flamboyant women.
The kind that waltz into restaurants
like they own it.
The kind who grab you by the arm
and drag you all over the place.
The kind that laughs out loud.
The kind of woman
that's… constantly managing.
And organizing things.
With no table manners.
Stuffing themselves
like they were starving.
And had just come off a hunger strike!
Slobbering on her fingers.
sucking and biting and licking.
And lapping up juices on her lips.
But today…
I have finally perceived
the poetry and the beauty of it all.
Of Candela.
Nobody has fed me since I was 5 years old.
When my mother would play that game
of "open up. here comes the plane."
I would get anxious.
And yet. with Candela…
everything tasted glorious.
But that's not all.
After dinner. we went out for a walk…
with a bunny rabbit.
The furry kind.
Magical.
And I was enchanted. Its name is Pomelo.
Isn't that hilarious?
You wanna know something else?
She takes her bunny
for a morning stroll. every morning.
On a leash. like it's a German Shepherd.
to soak up the sun's energy.
Personally. I have never been
a great lover of animals.
Especially not rodents.
However… there I was.
playing in the grass.
bonding with a bunny.
Everything that I believed
to be vulgar before…
Well. now I feel a magnetic attraction.
What I once thought to be obnoxious
and ostentatious.
in fact. turned out to be a hymn to life.
No more shrinking from life.
We must live…
our lives fully and completely to exist!
And play with rabbits.
I wanted to share this news with you.
in case you might be worried about
who I fall in love with for our new job.
This is nothing
like what happened in Paris.
And has nothing…
to do with the duchess's treasure.
Well. I'm going to use this fork. Mm?
You know. just in case you get excited.
watching me eating my food.
Mm.
It's true.
Quite often. opposites attract. Right?
- I'm just wondering how you got shot.
- Does it involve a bed and a boyfriend?
No. there is no boyfriend.
And there is no bed.
And no kissing either.
There was absolutely
nothing inappropriate between us.
I earned these bullet holes
simply because she caught me
foraging in her house.
And so. to celebrate this new philosophy.
we… we're gonna spend
the rest of our day exploring.
The Land Registry indicates that
the estate is made up of 8.300 hectares.
And that's the only info I got.
Google Earth doesn't even show images
from inside.
It's like it's a ghost estate.
There are a few photos of the winery.
They date back to the '60s.
It was a building with a large glass dome
in the middle of the countryside.
There was an underground cellar
used for fermenting the wines.
But the building was demolished years ago.
Shortly after he built that train line.
We have to find that wine cellar.
How do we do that?
Are we supposed to jump the fence?
We do it
with the newest member of the team.
The imperial Iberian eagle.
Today we'll just do a flyover.
Let's do this.
Up. up. and away.
Keila. head west. please.
Once we locate the family home.
we'll be able to find our bearings.
What's that?
Keila. zoom in.
Dead animals. And lots of them.
There's an electric fence.
It would appear this one has
much higher voltage than usual fences.
Current above 30 milliamps
is enough to cause a heart attack.
Look. There's something
behind those olive trees there.
That's the family home.
Cameron. find it on the map.
You gotta be kidding.
He has his own bullring?
Get closer. Let's see how His Highness
keeps himself entertained.
Zoom in all the way.
- Pull back.
- It looks like the train leaves from here.
So the wine cellar must be
within a one-kilometer radius at most.
And somewhere within that area.
there's an air vent.
Every underground construction.
by law. has to have a vent.
So if we can locate it.
then theoretically.
all we have to do is draw
a straight line from it to the home.
Then we'll find the cellar.
Wait. Stop there.
Zoom in.
The ventilation shaft.
Cameron. get the coordinates.
Draw a line from the house to the vent…
and keep going.
It seems to be the same glass dome
from the old building.
Minus the building.
Who would hide their treasure
under a glass dome?
That would be someone
with a passion for art and for poetry
who knows that some things
are best appreciated
only in natural light.
Such as… rare sapphires
or a giant blue diamond.
Or… just maybe.
a stupendous. wonderful work of art.
Don't you feel that insatiable desire
to discover what's hidden down there?
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
It's not responding to my commands.
We're losing altitude. It's dropping fast.
It's gone rogue.
The connection is unstable.
- What's going on?
- I'm not sure. but we've gone blind.
Sixty meters and falling.
They most likely have jammers.
The drone frequency is high.
but it doesn't seem to be enough.
- Keila. bring it in now!
- Thirty meters…
- I'm doing what I can.
- Twenty meters…
The GPS is working.
The drone isn't that far from us.
- It's nosediving.
- Ten meters…
Keila. it's almost on the ground.
Try to make it land.
The eagle's down.
Do you hear that?
Turn up the volume.
It's the fucking cattle.
They're scratching and sniffing the drone.
- We need to get it back immediately.
- No.
Going inside that place
without a plan would be suicide.
And I'm not talking
about the electric fences.
This duke isn't
your typical entitled nobleman.
He's a criminal!
Precisely.
So what do you think he'll do
when he finds a drone on his property?
Oh! Wait…
Maybe this cute drone belongs to the guy
who's interested in my art collection
and who also has a gang of thieves!
If that happens. him going to the police
will be the least of our worries.
Because his only other option is murder.
I'll go get it.
I'm sure I can locate it pretty fast
using the GPS coordinates.
No. no. no. no. Keila. no.
If you go. I'm going with you.
That was a sophisticated drone.
yet they managed to jam it.
So your earpieces
most likely won't function.
Out there. you'll be on your own.
We'll keep a close eye on you.
If you see anything unusual.
don't take any risks.
You immediately turn back.
Over there.
Careful. Slowly.
Can either one of you tell me
why I agreed
that Keila would go fetch the lost drone?
I mean. obviously she's the one
with the most brains here.
Because if I sent you or him.
chances are that sooner or later.
both of you
will tear each other to pieces.
Ever since you got here.
it's been nothing but long faces
and insults…
What makes you think any of us want
to listen and put up with your bullshit?
It's obvious you've broken the rules.
Sure. but to be fair.
Bruce and Keila broke them too.
No. they've managed to stay content.
So. I am going to ask you two
two questions.
Firstly. do you want to remain
in this gang?
Please answer me now.
Yes.
Good. And for my second question.
Imagine if you had to infiltrate
something like a train.
Yeah. Like the Orient Express.
for example.
And then. imagine that you had
to pretend to be a couple
and spend the night together
in the same bed.
Would you do it?
Yes.
No.
I don't know what happened between you.
But what I do know
is that both of you are 25 years old.
you have four million euros each.
you're beautiful.
healthy. and full of energy…
And even though you have it all.
you managed to screw it up!
- Over there. you see it?
- Yeah.
Bruce…
Okay. listen to me.
You sprained your ankle. and it's bad.
- It really hurts.
- Hide it.
- This is private property.
- I'm really sorry.
We came here to photograph the bulls.
and my girlfriend fell
and sprained her ankle.
You need to be careful where you walk.
It can be dangerous.
I guess you didn't see
all the no trespassing signs
around the property?
If I see anything moving here…
I pull out my weapon. and I shoot to kill.
You wanted to see the bulls?
Yeah. to take some photos
in their habitat.
Perfect. Let me show you.
I feed them every day.
Now's the time to take those photos.
No longer up to it. I guess?
C'mon. Sit down over there.
Let me take a look at your ankle.
I've seen lots of sprains out hunting.
Sit down.
Let me see.
Gotta check for swelling.
- Does it hurt?
- Yes. A bit. yeah.
How much is a bit?
It's painful when I walk.
I'm sorry. but it looks. um… pretty bad.
It's quite a serious sprain.
Lucky for you. I have what it takes.
This is what I do to help… all my bitches.
Gently rubbing this in
helps relieve the swelling.
It's okay. kid. pull out your phone.
See if there's any signal.
C'mon.
Make your call!
Fuckin' do it!
No signal.
This entire area is off-grid.
Let's get you some help. C'mon.
No. there's really no need.
It's much better.
- No. no. c'mon. Let's go.
- I can walk now.
It's all good. man. I got this. okay?
Hey. I'll take care of her now.
Thank you so much.
Look. you see. I can just carry her
on my back. It's easy.
Then you must be stupid. kid.
How are you gonna carry her?
Shh!
Are you gonna jump the electric fence?
And the wall?
Easy. girls!
Get inside.
Go on. Inside.
And you… in the back.
Forget it. No way.
Keila. get out of there.
C'mon. open the door.
Open the door! The door. Keila!
- You need a key to open it.
- Open the door!
Please. sir.
Open the damn door!
Please let me out! Bruce!
Open it!
I help you.
and now you're giving me this shit?
Step away from the truck. right now. Easy.
Keep movin'.
Now turn around.
Bruce!
Keep walking. asshole.
Tell me what you're doing here.
One or two injured trespassers.
it's all the same to me.
Enough of this shit.
Keep walking.
- I said keep walking.
- Fine.
We broke in. Happy?
And now we'll leave like nothing happened.
- Let me get her.
- Don't fucking move!
One more step. and I'll shoot you.
Go on. Pull the trigger.
But you better not miss. man.
'Cause I'll smash your head in.
Oh. yeah?
Next shot. I'll blow your brains out.
So. kid… why are you here? Tell me now.
We're trying to locate the vent
to the duke's underground cellar.
Don't move! Or I'll shoot.
- We need to bring him with us.
- What are you saying?
- We have to go. get out of here!
- Calm down. Relax. calm down!
We have to.
If he dies. that makes me a murderer.
And if he actually survives.
he knows exactly why we're here.
But how would he know?
Because I told him.
Let's go.
How are we gonna get outta here?
- We'll have to carry him out.
- And how do we get him over the main gate?
Is he humming a tune?
Or does he have something to tell us?
Roi. see if he has a phone.
Well. he doesn't seem to have any friends.
There are no missed calls.
no new messages.
There are a few hours left before dawn.
But when morning comes.
we have to let the creep go.
and we need to get out of Seville.
So. where does that leave us?
Well. that means we have an opportunity.
We have an opportunity for what?
An opportunity
to pull off the robbery tonight.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-